9curry.com 2019-04-10

# Privacy Policy

## Introduction

This website, 9curry.com (the "Site") and its mobile applications (the "APP"), which is, with its owner and staff is collectively referred here as 9curry("9curry"). 9curry takes the private nature of your personal information very seriously.

This privacy policy, which we adapted from a policy originally provided by Automattic (WordPress.com), describes how we treat the information we collect when you visit and use our Site or APP and other Services. Please read this notice very carefully.

## Website Visitors

Like most website operators, 9curry collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. 9curry’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how 9curry’s visitors use its website, APP and services. From time to time, 9curry may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g. by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

9curry also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. 9curry does not use such information to identify its visitors, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

## Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors, users to 9curry’s websites or APP choose to interact with 9curry in ways that require 9curry to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that 9curry gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for 9curry.com to provide a username and email address and public profile on social network facebook. In each case, 9curry collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with 9curry. 9curry does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website/app related activities.

## Aggregated Statistics

9curry may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors, users to its websites, apps or services. For instance, 9curry may monitor the most popular posts or information on 9curry.com. 9curry may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, 9curry does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

## Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

9curry discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on 9curry’s behalf or to provide services available at 9curry’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using 9curry’s websites and applications, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. In addition, in some cases we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if 9curry or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that 9curry goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquiror of 9curry may continue to use your personal and non-personal information only as set forth in this policy. Otherwise, 9curry will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone.

Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, 9curry discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when 9curry believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of 9curry, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of a 9curry website/applications and have supplied your email address, 9curry may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with 9curry and its products. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. 9curry takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

You should also be aware that if you submit information to "chat rooms," "forums” or "message boards", "commenting" such information becomes public information, meaning that you lose any privacy rights you might have with regards to that information. Such disclosures may also increase your chances of receiving unwanted communications.

## Cookies and Usage Data.

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. 9curry uses cookies to help 9curry identify and track visitors, their usage of 9curry websites, and their website access preferences. 9curry visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using 9curry’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of 9curry’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

**What are cookies and similar technologies?**

A cookie is a small data file, often including a unique identifier, which is sent to your computer, mobile phone or tablet device (referred to in this policy as a “device”) by the web server so the website can remember some information about your browsing activity on the website. The cookie will collect information relating to your use of our Services, information about your device, e.g. the device’s IP address and browser type, broad location and, if you arrived at our site via a link from third party site, the URL of the linking page. If you have registered for any Services or you are a subscriber, it may also collect your name and email address, which may be transferred to data processors for registered user or subscriber verification purposes.

Similar technologies known as “local storage” may also be used in our Services as an alternative to cookies. This is technology which is similar to cookies and performs very similar functions, such as caching data to enable us to improve our Services, allowing you to register for our Services, tracking activity to enable us and our advertisers to advertise to you in accordance with this policy and counting the number of people who view adverts on our Services. Where we refer to “cookies” in this policy, we mean cookies or similar technologies.

Cookies record information about your online preferences and help us to tailor our Services to your interests. Information provided by cookies can help us to analyse your use of our Services and help us to provide you with a better user experience.

In addition to cookies, our Services may also use web beacons, clear GIFs, page tags and web bugs. These are all types of technology implemented by websites or third party ad servers to allow them to analyse your website use and help improve your experience of the Services.

**What are the different types of cookies?**

  * **Session cookies** are only stored for the duration of your visit to a website and are deleted from your device when you close your browser;
  * **Persistent cookies** are saved on your device for a fixed period of time after the browser has closed and are used where we (or a third party) need to identify you for a later browsing session. The fixed period of time is typically 30-90 days for targeting or behavioural advertising cookies and may be up to 26 months for analytical performance and measurement cookies;
  * **First party cookies** are set by the website you are visiting; and
  * **Third party cookies** are cookies used within our Services which are set by other organisations. These include cookies from external analytics services which help us to understand the use of our sites, or by advertisers so that they can track the effectiveness of their advertisements.

**What are cookies used for?**

1\. Functional Cookies Functional cookies are essential to the running of our Services. They are used to remember your preferences on our websites and to provide enhanced, more personal features. The information collected by these cookies is usually anonymised, so we cannot identify you personally. Functional cookies do not track your internet usage or gather information which could be used for selling advertising, but they do help with serving advertising. These cookies are usually session cookies which will expire when you close your browsing session.

2\. Essential or ‘Strictly Necessary’ Cookies These cookies are essential for the running of our Services. Without these cookies, parts of our websites would not function. These cookies do not track where you have been on the internet and do remember preferences beyond your current visit and do not gather information about you that could be used for marketing purposes. These cookies are usually session cookies which will expire when you close your browsing session.

3\. Analytical Performance and Measurement Cookies Analytical performance cookies are used to monitor the performance of our Services, for example, to determine the number of pageviews and the number of unique users a website has. Web analytics services may be designed and operated by third parties. The information provided by these cookies allows us to analyse patterns of user behaviour and we use that information to enhance user experience or identify areas of the website which may require maintenance. The information is anonymous (i.e. it cannot be used to identify you and does not contain personal information such as your name and email address) and it is only used for statistical purposes

4\. Targeting or ‘Behavioural Advertising’ Cookies These cookies, which may be placed on your device by us or our trusted third party service providers, remember that you have visited a website and use that information to provide you with content or advertising which is tailored to your interests. This is often called online behavioural advertising (OBA) and is done by grouping together shared interests based upon web browsing history. Your web browsing history can be used to infer things about you (e.g. your age, gender etc.), and this information may also be used to make advertising on websites more relevant to you. Without these cookies, content and advertisements you encounter may be less relevant to you and your interests. If you would like more information about OBA, including how to opt-out of these cookies, please visit: <http://www.youronlinechoices.com/> or scroll down to: **How can users manage or opt out of cookies?**

**How does 9curry use cookies?**

9curry, together with our trusted partners, uses cookies in combination with other information we maintain for a number of purposes, including the following:

1\. Essential and Functional Cookies We use these cookies to enable certain online functionality including:

  * access your information so we can provide you with customised content and experiences, or remember the last page you visited on the Services;
  * identify returning users, registrants and subscribers and allow them to be presented with a personalised version of the site;
  * eliminating the need for returning users to re-enter their login details;
  * commenting on our sites;
  * operating a shopping trolley on various of our Services including www.myfavouritemagazines.com;
  * maintain your settings and authenticate your identity while you are logged in to the Services;
  * to support security measures and to assist in identifying possible fraudulent or abusive activities.

If you object to the use of essential and functional cookies please scroll down to: **How can users manage or opt out of cookies?**

2\. Analytical Performance and Measurement Cookies

We use these cookies to measure users’ behaviour to better develop our Services. By using analytics services provided by third parties such as Google Analytics and ComScore, we can analyse and measure which pages are viewed and how long for and which links are followed, and we can use this information to provide more content which is of interest. We also use this analysis to report on our performance and to sell advertising.

If you object to the use of analytical performance and measurement cookies please see here: **How can users manage or opt out of cookies?**

3\. Targeting and Behavioural Advertising Cookies

We use these cookies to:

  * manage online advertising and revenue share arrangements. Our approved advertising partners, primarily Google (Doubleclick, AdX, AdSense), Rubicon Project, Index Exchange, AppNexus, OpenX, Pubmatic, Criteo and GroupM use cookies together with web beacons to provide advertising to you and to enable us to manage our relationship with those advertisers by, for example, tracking how many unique users have seen a particular advertisement or followed a link in an advertisement;
  * manage eCommerce activities via affiliate links and associated revenue share arrangements;
  * measure general user behaviour across our sites and third party sites to build a profile based on users browsing patterns so that we and third parties can target advertising to users that will be more relevant to users’ interests. This means that if, for example, users visit a page with a review about a particular camera then the cookie will collect this information and we may target adverts for that camera to those users and, if users visit third party sites that are part of the same advertising network, those third parties may target adverts for that camera to those users;
  * to create profiles that trusted third parties can buy to allow them to better target their advertising with more relevant content; and
  * keep track of the number of users who saw a particular ad or visited a particular page of one of our websites, analyse the effectiveness of our ads, and provide auditing, research and reporting for advertisers.

The trusted partners we work with in relation to targeting and behavioural advertising include third-party ad servers, ad agencies, technology vendors, providers of advertisement content, research firms and other companies that help us provide more effective advertising and offer you a more personalised experience. As your browser, app or device communicates with the third party’s servers, these companies can collect information, including your IP address, page header information, browser or device information, just as if you had requested their web page or used their apps directly. We cannot control nor do we have access to any cookies placed on your computer by third party advertisers and sponsors.

If you object to the use of targeting and behavioural advertising cookies please scroll down to: **How can users manage or opt out of cookies?**

## Third Party Services

You may notice on some pages of our websites that cookies have been set that are not related to 9curry. When you visit a page with content embedded from, for example, YouTube or Facebook, these third party service providers may set their own cookies on your device. 9curry does not control the use of these third party cookies and cannot access them due to the way that cookies work, as cookies can only be accessed by the party who originally set them. Please check the third party websites for more information about these cookies.

These services may use cookies and usage data to track and serve better and relevant Advertisements and provide statistics for helping us tailer and improve user experience and our website and serve relevant content to users by tracking their experience, interests and usage. This doesn't include personally identifiable information about the user e.g. name of the user. We also use One Signal services to provide users alerts/notifications, which tracks user interests and subscriptions. This also don't include personally identifiable information other than the interests user shows in our services and only used to provide better experience and improve engagement of the users on our website. e.g. If the user wants to subscribe our notifications they may do and can easily unsubscribe by going to their browser settings and removing notification service for the website. You agree with use of these third party services & their cookie and privacy policies.

We do use Google services like Adsense and Analytics etc. [How Google uses information from sites or apps that use Google services?](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites)

We use cloudflare & Fastly as our CDN providers, which too use cookies to provide services. [Cloudflare’s EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework Statement](https://www.cloudflare.com/privacyshield/), [Cloudflare Cookie Policy](https://www.cloudflare.com/cookie-policy/), [Fastly Privacy Policy](https://www.fastly.com/privacy) and [Fastly Cookie Policy](https://www.fastly.com/cookies)

## Ads

Ads appearing on any 9curry websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies as mentioned above. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy covers the use of cookies by 9curry and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

## Links to Third Party Sites

This privacy policy only applies to information collected by 9curry. This privacy policy does not apply to the practices of companies that 9curry does not own or control, or employees that 9curry does not manage. A 9curry website may contain links to third party websites. Any information you provide to, or that is collected by, third-party sites may be subject to the privacy policies of those sites, if any. We encourage you to read such privacy policies of any third-party sites you visit. It is the sole responsibility of such third parties to adhere to any applicable restrictions on the disclosure of your personally-identifying information, and 9curry and its affiliates shall not be liable for wrongful use or disclosure of your personally-identifying information by any third party.

## Security

All non-personally-identifying information, potentially personally-identifying and personally identifying-information described above is stored on restricted database servers.

## Choice/Opt-out

**How can users manage or opt out of cookies:** If we ever send you information by email concerning new products, services or information that you did not expressly request, we will provide you with an email address by which you may request no further notices.

Some people find the idea of a website storing information on their device a little intrusive, in particular when the information is stored and used by a third party. For example, you may object to being served advertising which is targeted to your interests based on your browsing history. If you would prefer to opt out of cookies, it is possible to control cookies by following the steps below, however you should be aware that you might lose some features and functionality of the website if you do so.

Cookies, including those which have already been set, can be deleted from your hard drive. You can also change the preferences/settings in your web browser to control cookies. Some internet browsers have a ‘Do Not Track or ‘DNT’ setting; this sends a signal to websites asking them not to track your browsing. The following links may be helpful:

In some cases, you can choose to accept cookies from the primary site, but block them from third parties. In others, you can block cookies from specific advertisers, or clear out all cookies. Deleting or blocking cookies may reduce functionality of the site. To learn more about how to reject cookies, visit <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/> or go to the help menu within your internet browser. If you experience any problems having deleted cookies, you should contact the supplier of your web browser.

For more information about third party cookies generated by advertisers please visit [www.youronlinechoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/).

Please be aware that these are third party websites and 9curry does not accept any liability for the instructions given on these sites.

Opting out of Analytical Performance Cookies: If you would like to opt out of Analytics cookies, please do so by clicking on the relevant links in this Third Party Cookies table here.

Opting out of Targeting and Behavioural Advertising Cookies: If you would like to disable third party cookies generated by advertisers or providers of targeted advertising services, you can turn them off by going to the third party’s website. Please click here for details.

You can find out how to decline targeting and behavioural advertising cookies by visiting: <http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/> [http://www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/) [http://www.youronlinechoices.eu](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)

Web Beacons You can normally render web beacons and other tracking technologies ineffective by switching off cookies in your browser. There are also browser add-ons and extensions that specifically block web beacons. If you object to web beacons in emails, we recommend that you follow the instructions for deleting existing cookies and disabling 9curry cookies above. We will still know how many of our emails are opened and we will automatically receive your IP address, a unique identifier of your device or other access device; but we will not identify you as an individual.

## Address Book Data

Any external address book data (email contacts, etc.) that a user voluntarily gives 9curry access to will only be used for the described feature (looking up friends, etc.), and will not be stored or repurposed.

## Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, 9curry may change its privacy policy from time to time, and in 9curry’s sole discretion. 9curry encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its privacy policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this privacy policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

## Contact Us

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our sites in general, please contact us.
